her alarm clock.
"9:25
am..."
She read out quietly.
She looked around her room, looking
at the writings on it.
Oh
yeah...
That's right.
I'm back.
A small and faint smile appeared on her lips.
She got out of bed and went over to the
window to look outside.
She pulled it up to open it, sticking her head out
to feel the cool fresh air.
Once the cold wind hit her skin, a very satisfied
smile grew on her lips as she closed her eyes to feel
everything around her.
After a moment of peace and quietness, she opened
her blue eyes and looked over to the Aarons's
house, basically Jess's room.
"Maybe he's still sleeping..."
She mumbled to herself, seeing that the
lights were still off in his room.
After a while of watching the window she found herself to
be feeling creepy so she stepped back and took a breath
before going to her closet to get a new set of clothes to
wear for today.
As soon as she finished making her bed and tidying herself
up, she slowly crept down the stairs and headed to the
kitchen to have her breakfast.
"Hey honey," she heard Judy's voice as she entered the
living room, finding her mother sitting on the couch,
drinking a cup of coffee while Bill was in the kitchen,
making breakfast.
"Good morning!"
"Morning Judy, Bill."
Leslie chirped as she went over to hug her before going to
the kitchen and hugging Bill behind.
"So did you sleep well?"
Bill asked her with a chuckle as she took her
seat behind the dining table, waiting for her
breakfast to be done.
"It was okay I guess."
She shrugged her shoulders.
Bill set her plate on the table and then went over to the
living room to give Judy's hers.
"The bed was really comfy!"
She showed a goofy grin.
"So is Jess coming over today?"
Judy came to the kitchen with her breakfast
and her coffee in her hands.
She took a seat opposite to Leslie and
started eating her breakfast.
"Yeah," she said, stuffing in the
pan cakes in her mouth.
"He said he would."
She continued after swallowing her food.
The rest of their breakfast was lively and chatty, with
laughter filling up the the table.
"So what'd you do with Leslie yesterday?"
May Belle excitedly asked her brother as
their family ate their breakfast.
"We went
to..."
He showed her the look, giving a grin.
He couldn't let their parents
know about it, ever.
It was just his, May Belle's and of
course, Leslie's place.
"So I'm guessing that Leslie girl is
looking pretty," said Ellie, pouring
Joyce Ann some milk in her bowl.
"It was pretty clear that she'd turn into a
beauty when we saw her."
Brenda nodded her head along with a grin.
Jess chocked on his own food, going into
fits of cough, making him drink his glass
of water finished.
"Ooo Mommy! Jess is choking!"
Joyce Ann pointed at his brother with a giggle.
"Jess, eat your food properly," his mother said, patting her
son's back before handling her children's finished dishes
and going to the sink to wash them.
"You're going to Leslie's later right?"
"Yeah," Jess laid his head down
on the wooden table.
"I can right?"
"Sure."
Said his mother.
"Who's this Leslie? I wanna meet her!"
Joyce Ann whined.
Oh yeah, she never got to meet
Leslie before in person.
Maybe as a baby, but she was too young
to even remember it.
May Belle turned to her, rolling her eyes.
She always didn't like Joyce Ann because now that she's grown
older, Joyce Ann was their little girl now.
"You can't meet her," she snickered.
"She doesn't
want to."
"What?"
Joyce Ann got teary eyed once she
heard May Belle's words.
She turned to her mom with a pout.
"Is that true mommy?"
The siblings chuckled at their baby
sister's innocent nature.
Jess couldn't help but feel a bit pity for Joyce Ann
since May Belle was so mean to her.
"Of course not hunny," their mother said,
caressing her daughter's cheek.
"Leslie's a good girl. I'm
sure she'll like you."
Jess raised his head up and rested his chin on the palm of
his hand as he looked at Joyce Ann.
"May Belle's just kidding
Joyce, Leslie loves kids."
He gave her a reassuring smile as he got up from the table
and went to Joyce Ann's side to give her a peck on her cheek
and then ruffling May Belle's hair before heading
towards the door.
"I'll come back later, see ya guys."
"Don't stay out too long, you still
have chores to do later."
He heard his father's voice as he left the house.
He quickly walked to the Burke's property,
rushing to see Leslie again.
Best friends right?
A knock came upon the door, turning
heads towards the entrance.
"That must be Jess!"
Leslie whispered sharply with excitement in her
voice, getting up from the table.
"Slow down lil girl!"
She could hear Bill talking as she
walked towards the door.
She then opened the door, revealing Jess who had his hands
behind his back as if he was trying to look formal and
respectful for whatever reason.
"What's the occasion?"
She laughed, pulling him inside a moment later.
Jess gladly let her lead him to the kitchen
where the Burke's were likely at.
"Good morning Jess."
Bill greeted him with a small smile.
Judy nodded her head and returned back to eating.
"Good morning Bill," Jess said.
He turned to Judy, unsure if he was supposed to
call her Mrs Burke or just Judy.
They rarely conversed with each other and when they
did, it was just for a brief moment.
Judy raised her head to him and smiled.
"Judy," she said.
" Just call me Judy, Jess."
Jess nodded his head.
"Good morning Judy."
He couldn't help but blush when he called
Leslie's mom by her first name.
It just didn't sit right with him!
Nevertheless, he continued with
the informal greetings.
"Come on!"
Leslie grabbed his arm and ran
to the door before Jess could
even properly bid goodbye to
the Burke's .
They trailed along the stream, walking towards the path to
Terabithia except this was a way that they had never gone to
before when they were kids.
"So where are we going today?"
Leslie walked in front of him and then carefully
jumped to the river and hopped onto the rocks,
getting across the other side.
Although the water wasn't rapid or that
deep, it still looked risky enough to not
dare to jump across.
"It's
a
secret..."
Jess whispered, trying to hide his fear from her as
he tried to jump across as well.
It wasn't that he was afraid.
He had done this before, alone, when he
was just wondering around.
But now that Leslie was back, he was more cautious of things
especially when it has something to do with her.
He carefully jumped onto the rocks, skipping
some along the way to quicken the time to get to the
other side with Leslie.
After doing so, he told Leslie to come along and ran
towards the deeper ends of the forest.
In a minute or so, they arrived at a foot of
a huge tree where an old tree house could
be seen on it.
Near the tree house were ropes to climb to get up from
below and climb up to the tree house.
The most noticeable thing was that even though the house
itself looked old, there was a sign at the front where it had the
words painted - 'nothing crushes us' and had a painting of
swords and shields on it.
"What's this?"
Leslie showed him a confused expression.
Jess went closer to the tree and then took the rope,
gesturing for her to take it so she can go up.
Leslie crinkled her nose and then shook her
head, pushing away the rope.
"I'll climb it up myself."
"Really?"
"What's the matter? It's just climbing."
She started climbing up, ignoring the dirt
that was dirtying her clothes.
As she reached the end and went to the tree house
itself, Jess followed behind by using his
usual route - the rope.
"Is this yours?"
She asked as they came into the room.
"Ours actually," Jess corrected her, leaning on the
wall as she continued to look around.
He blushed when Leslie picked up
his teddy bear, blue.
"That-that was actually yours-"
Leslie looked back at him and then giggled, "I may not
remember Terabithia, but I still do remember what I
owned and liked," she placed the toy on top of her head
and fiddled with it.
"Besides, it's really cute!"
Jess blushed as they continued to walk around the room.
Leslie suddenly laughed as she looked at the drawings that
she and Jess made when they were younger.
"I was such a goof back then," she giggled, staring at her
drawings and then looking at Jess's.
"So what happened to your drawings?
Have you made any progress?"
Jess blushed and shrugged his shoulders.
"I don't know," he scratched his cheek.
"I have some drawings that I made a few
months ago in my room."
Leslie grinned at him, "you better show
'em to me later after this."
She continued scanning around the room and noticed a
paper that didn't seem familiar to her.
"Okay I know that
I'm not really
good at drawing
but..."
She pointed to the paper and
wore a confused face.
"I'm sure that
my drawing
isn't this...
Well..."
"Kiddish like it was drawn by a 7 yr old?"
He cut her off with a chuckle.
He walked to her and then traced his fingers along the drawing and
then pointed with his thumb to a wooden box.
"May Belle drew it," he got down and then
took a magnifying glass out of the box and
handed it over to her.
She raised her eye brow in question before
taking it from him and placing it to her eye and
analyzing the drawing.
"Drawn by May belle..."
She read out quietly.
A small smile grew on her lips, placing the
magnifying glass on top of the wooden box.
Jess looked at her uneasily as he
ruffled his brown hair.
"You're not mad are you?"
"Mad?"
Her tone as if surprised by his question.
"Why would I be mad?"
She put her hands behind her back and
walked out of the room.
Jess slowly walked behind her
and leaned on the wall.
"Well..."
He trailed off as his eyes looked around the forest,
trying to think of an excuse to say.
"I
don't
know..."
Leslie looked back at him with a goofy grin.
"The more the merrier right? Can't believe
you'd think that I'd be angry about this," she
said in a jokingly manner.
She looked at the ground and stared at it for a while.
There was a moment of silence as she thought.
Finally, Jess asked her, "what are you doing?"
"Can you actually jump from here and land safely to the
ground with the Terabithia Magic?"
She asked without turning around.
Jess started walking over to her, still
confused by her question.
"Well
yeah
but.."
Before he could even finish, Leslie decided to do the most
stupidest thing that could be done at the moment.
Without another second thought, she jumped from the
tree house, Jess's eyes widening in shock as he
watched her escape from his sight.
"Leslie-!"
He immediately jumped to the edge to see if she was
alright, injured, or even worse.
His eyes darted over to the blonde girl who was
smiling at him with her arms wide open.
The 2 best friends walked to the bridge, chatting away happily with laughter filling up the place.
She finally remembered.
She remembered Terabithia.
"You almost gave me a heart attack
you know," Jess joked.
"That was my plan."
Leslie laughed as she playfully
pushed him away with one hand.
They continued with their playful antics to each
other before arriving to the bridge.
As they walked over to the bridge, a thunder roared
across the sky, making them both look up.
The clouds were getting darker and darker by the second and the
wind was getting chillier and chillier.
Jess looked over at Leslie who seemed to be feeling colder
by the minute as she cuddled herself.
He was wearing a jacket, just in case if the situation
ever ends up like this but Leslie, she was wearing her
usual eccentric style of clothing, except that her
jacket was missing.
He then went behind her and took off his jacket, wrapping
it around her shivering shoulders.
Leslie gave him a questioning look before
reluctantly using his jacket.
"Thanks," she smiled.
"But what about you?"
Jess started walking forward, "I'm a
guy, this is nothing to me."
Before they even knew it, rain drops started coming
down, and soon the heavy rain came after.
They dashed across the bridge and then to the hills,
and later arriving at the road.
To be fair, the Aarons's house were nearer
so they decided to head back to Jess's place
together instead.
Jess shook his head vigorously as he let the
water fall from his hair.
He took off his shoes and placed them to the shoe
box before opening the door.
Leslie did the same thing and
then entered his house.
"You're back so soon?"
They heard Ellie's voice.
She peered over her shoulder and looked at Jess,
not noticing Leslie's presence.
"Dry yourself up dude."
She rolled her eyes and went back
to watching the TV.
Leslie looked at Jess with an eye brow raised before
whispering, "does she know I'm here?"
Jess looked at her and shrugged his shoulders.
In a minute or so, realization hit Ellie.
She looked back at them with eyes wide open
before looking at Leslie.
"Oh you're here!"
"Who's here?"
They heard Jess's mom, Mary, speak all
the way from the kitchen.
A few seconds later, she came out
and approached them.
"Oh, Leslie!"
Ellie, just then noticing that they were both
soaking wet, jumped up to her feet and went to her
bedroom to get some stuff.
"My you 2 are dripping wet!"
Mary ushered them to the couch, not
giving a care if it'd get wet.
Ellie then rushed down from the stairs
with 2 towels in her hand.
She threw the blue one over to Jess and gently handed over the
red one to Leslie before going back up.
As Leslie took off Jess's jacket, she walked
around shyly and then looked at Mary.
"Where should I put this mam?"
She asked politely.
"Just put it over the rack Leslie," Mary responded with a
small smile as she dialed the Burke's to make sure they knew
that Leslie was at their place.
"Yes hello, this is Mrs
Aarons- Mary. Yes, I'm
just calling to inform
you that..."
Leslie returned back to Jess's side after
putting his jacket on the racket.
She looked at the window, looking at
how heavy the rain was.
Didn't seem like she was going to go
home any sooner now.
"Hey mom, Joyce needs some help with her assignment about
some family history or something..."
They could hear Brenda speaking as
she went down the stairs.
She looked over to Jess and then to Leslie before
looking at her mom who was over the phone and then
to Leslie again.
"Oh."
She mouthed.
She gave Leslie a warm smile before
quickly going back up.
It just felt weird for a girl that was
Jess's age to be in the house.
"Yes,
okay-"
Mary put down the phone and then
turned to Jess and Leslie.
"You kids can take a bath upstairs," she
went back to the phone again.
Both of them took Mary's word and headed upstairs with
the towels wrapped around their body.
As they came into the hallway of the rooms, Leslie
asked Jess, "so who's going first?"
Jess headed for his room.
"You go. Ladies first right?"
He smirked before opening the door and then entering it.
Leslie smiled at him and then headed to the bathroom,
closing it and then locking it later.
Jess collapsed to his bed, ignoring how
wet his bed would be later.
He stared at at the ceiling, his towel
draped around his neck.
Who would've thought, that a girl, Leslie for that matter,
was going to take a SHOWER in his house!
Sure, they've slept together when they were kids
at the tree house in Terabithia before since they
were still innocent little kids but now, they're
all grown up.
Mature.
At that phase.
"Oh lord you seriously have to stop it Jess!"
He hissed darkly, pulling his
hair in frustration.
He sat up and looked at the door, any moment now she could
just come in with whatever she's going to wear with her
dripping wet and all.
What is he talking about, girls take VERY long in the bathroom...
He let out a sigh and then got up, going to the small box he had underneath his study table.
Leslie slowly took off her clothes and put
them on the racket near the tub.
As she turned on the shower, water droplets dropped,
sliding on her smooth and frail skin.
She closed her eyes as she felt the small drops sliding off,
her hair getting wetter and wetter.
"Leslie?"
She heard a knock coming from the door.
She looked over to the door and then
closed the curtains.
"Yes?"
"It's me Ellie. I just came to drop you off some old
clothes of mine, can I come in?"
Leslie turned off the shower and then wrapped the towel
around her body before unlocking the door.
Ellie quickly went in and then locked the door before
placing the set of clothes near the sink.
"Thank you."
Leslie wore a smile before going into the shower
and then taking off he towel.
She put her arm out with the
towel in her hand, "can you
erm..."
"I got it," Ellie responded and took the towel,
putting it back to the rack again.
As she did so, she looked over to Leslie, a
thought appearing in her mind.
"Say, we have this sort of Aaron's tradition
and," a smirk grew on her lips.
"We scrub the girls' back when we're taking a bath,
it's a family tradition for girls."
Ellie pushed aside the curtain
and went behind Leslie.
"Hope you don't mind," she grabbed the scrub.
A sharp gasp escaped Ellie's lips when
she looked at Leslie's back.
"Leslie...
You-"
"I
know..."
Leslie peered over her shoulder and
looked at Ellie with a sad smile.
"Don't tell anyone, please?"
The door opened, making Jess
immediately turn to the door.
Leslie then entered his room, wearing an
oversized red T-shirt that Ellie wore last time
and a rather very SHORT shorts.
Her towel was hanging around her neck, her hair
still a bit wet from the shower.
"Guess I hogged up the bathroom huh."
She chuckled as she walked around his room and looked at the
furniture and the stuff on his wall.
Jess shook his head and then ruffled
his almost dry wet hair.
"Well you were
certainly
long..."
He trailed and got up from his bed,
heading out to the bathroom.
He looked at Leslie again who was comfortably
walking around and touching his stuff.
He didn't mind.
At least if it's Leslie
touching them that is.
As Leslie walked around the room, looking
at his furniture, Jess slowly closed the
door and then left.
She peered over her shoulder to make sure that he was gone
before going to his bed and lying on it.
"Wow..."
She sighed.
It made her feel weird lying down on his
bed, much less a BOY's bed.
Ew don't think about such things, he's your best friend!
She rolled her eyes and then looked up to the
ceiling and then sat up.
She looked at the walls, noticing that there were
quite an amount of drawings on it.
The only thing that seemed to change in Jess's room was that there
was a couple of rock bands posters on it.
As she looked around, a small
book got her attention.
She got up and then walked to his study table
where the small book was.
It seemed familiar.
She took the dusty book and opened it, making
the dust waft into her face.
"Ehem, ehem," she grunted as she
tried to clear my throat.
What the heck?
Why is this so dusty?
She looked at the page and saw drawings,
very creative drawings.
She flipped some more and found that as the more she went
deeper, the drawings were becoming sketches.
From weird creative drawings to more realism.
She finally turned to the last page, finding a
realism drawing, a very good one of a girl with short
hair who looked like her.
"Is
this
me...?"
Leslie mumbled.
She set the book down and looked at the walls again.
Her eyes found itself looking at that one drawing where it
seemed like color pencils were used.
It was a tree house drawing, their tree
house household on Terabithia!
She smiled as she looked at the rest of his things when
suddenly she heard the door open.
"Took you long," she chuckled,
approaching the wet haired Jess.
"I thought boys were suppose to be fast."
Jess dried his hair up with the towel,
"you took longer you know."
He grinned as he walked to his bed and sat on it
while Leslie went to the study table and sat on
the office chair.
"So what happened to Ms Edmunds?"
Leslie suddenly asked.
Jess stared at her with a puzzled face.
Why suddenly the question?
"She married some guy and moved to New York..."
He closed his eyes and folded his arms.
"She has a kid now."
Leslie raised her eye brow and then smirked.
"Bet that you got jealous when you heard that she got married
huh," she chuckled and then leaned forward.
"I still remember how you stared at her in class as if she
was some goddess or something."
A blush crept to Jess's cheeks as Leslie
continued teasing him about his crush
with the music teacher.
"You were just staring at her like some creepy kid while the
rest of us were getting the instruments!"
She laughed and then tried to make a face that
Jess was wearing at the time.
"You told me that that time to take a picture cause
it'd last longer," Jess grinned.
He then looked over his shoulder and looked at his pillow.
Just for fun, he took the pillow and then showed a
mischievous face before throwing it to her face.
"Pillow fight Les!"
"What-" she yelped as the pillow hit her.
A big smile grew on her lips.
She got up to her feet and then grabbed the pillow, running to Jess
before hitting him with it relentlessly.
"Ha ha ha!"
She laughed as she hit him straight in the face.
Jess smirked at her and then shoved
the pillow to her face.
"Got
ya!"
Leslie leaned on him and then smacked him
with the pillow for payback.
As Jess leaned back, he unintentionally
grabbed Leslie's wrist and pulled her down
to him, making them both lie in bed on top of
each other.
The fits of laughter died down and instead,
there was a moment of silence, though Leslie
was wearing a small smile.
Jess stared at Leslie's blue green orbs,
completely taken away by the moment.
He could smell her strawberry scent shampoo,
her breath touching his skin.
He was too afraid to even breathe, fearing
that it might ruin the moment.
Wait what moment?
Their lips were just a few inches apart and
they just couldn't move.
"Leslie-!"
The door opened ever so loudly, revealing May
Belle with a big smile on her face.
That is until she saw the position of the 2
favorite people she looks up to.
Leslie stuck her tongue out before pushing herself off of
Jess upon seeing May Belle's appearance.
"Hey May Belle!"
She beamed, clearing her throat.
She averted Jess's gaze and got up,
walking to May Belle.
Jess continued staring at Leslie
before shaking his head.
God damn what was he doing?
He swore this
happens too much...
He cleared his throat abruptly and then stood up.
"So, ahem," the girls looked at him.
He opened his words but his throat felt
parched and so, no words came out.
"I'm-I'm gonna go down to get some drink- ye-yeah."
He awkwardly made his way to the door
and left the girls alone.
When they heard Jess go down the stairs, May Belle closed
the door and then turned to Leslie.
"So what was that I saw earlier?"
She smirked, leaning her body on the
door with her arms crossed.
She just heard that Leslie came over and figured that she'd
be in Jess's room, but never did she think that she'd see them
in a position like that.
Leslie let out a sigh and sat on Jess's bed.
She tossed her head back and crossed her arms.
What was she suppose to say, Jess pulled me
over and we almost kissed?
Hell no.
"Pillow fight."
She said.
"Yeah, pillow fight. That's what it was."
Jess shook his head hopelessly.
He pushed his hair back and let his head
thud against the wall.
He closed his eyes and enjoyed the
precious silence he had.
"Get your head straight Jess," he muttered.
"You can't possibly like her."
The only reason why Jess was refusing to accept
the fact that he liked her, was because he knew
that it was impossible.
It was impossible for her to like him and he
was afraid of rejection.
When he presumed that she had 'died' and well
left him, he became different.
He started doing stupid stuff and
dating several girls.
He was afraid that he'd hurt Leslie, the way
he hurt those other girls.
Stupid right?
He let out a soft sigh and opened his brown
eyes, staring at the stairs.
Those falls were happening too much.
He walked to the refrigerator and
got a glass of water.
He slurped them all up and set the glass down.
"What's the matter now," his father's voice said.
He looked at where the voice was coming from and found his father
walking towards him with a strict face.
"You only do that when you're stressed over something."
Jess shook his head to his father.
"It's nothing."
"Doesn't seem like nothing."
His father lowered his voice as he walked past him and got a
glass of juice before sitting down.
"So tell me, what's the problem?"
He stated.
Jess pulled a seat out and then sat on it.
He rested his chin on the palm of his
hand before responding.
"It's Leslie..."
His father seemed to be take a back
from his response.
He raised his eye brow and said, "what
about the Burke girl?"
Burke girl...
Jess managed to let a smirk come to his lips.
"I
think..."
He trailed.
"I think that I..."
He drifted his words and looked at his father who
looked as if he was getting impatient.
"I think I like her."
He finally said.
His father leaned back on the chair
and crossed his arms.
His son likes his best friend.
What a complicated situation.
Especially with his kind.
He looked at his son who looked confused over
his feelings towards Leslie.
He cleared his throat, "so what's the
problem with liking her?"
His tone sounded more like a demand
rather than a question.
"The problem is that I can't like her."
Jess almost yelled.
He didn't understand it himself, but
he just couldn't like her.
Maybe the thing with Leslie was just puppy love like the
same with Miss Edmunds, nothing more.
Maybe it'd pass over time.
With that being said, Jess shook his head.
"I didn't mean it that way," he sighed.
"Leslie's my friend. My best
friend. That's all she is."
His father looked at him for a minute
before letting out a sigh.
"You really won't know if you like a girl. You might
like her as a friend, or your best friend, or even as
a girl. You won't really know until the right time
comes."
Jess raised his head up and looked
at his father's face.
His father had a point.
Maybe what he was feeling is just normal.
Normal for a guy his age to care
about his best friend.
And obviously a teenaged guy like him will blush at situations
where their faces are very close to each other.
"Thanks dad," he said, letting a
smirk grow on his lips.
"Didn't know that you could give advice like this
since you've always been that sorta-"
"Well you're old man's gotten lot of
experience," his father abruptly stood up and
drank all the juice in his glass.
"I need to go for another shift now."
He ruffled his son's hair and retreated back to the living room to
kiss his wife before leaving the house.
As he watched his father's truck drive
away from the land and onto the road, a
realization struck him.
He knew that Leslie liked to poke into his things when they
were younger so it's likely that she'll still do the same
thing, maybe even worser.
His eyes darted to the stairs.
He had to hide it before Leslie or even
May Belle could find it.
Beneath his bed,
was his dirty
little stash...
He's a boy, what would you expect.
He quickly rushed up to the stairs, not too
quickly as the girls might hear him but still
quick enough for he was anxious that they'd find
it any minute now.
Leslie did like to poke around people's things.
Well, just the people she's close to.
Knowing that Jess was still downstairs and won't be coming
up anytime soon, the 2 girls went around his room, trying to
find for anything dirty.
"How old are you again May Belle?"
Leslie asked as she opened a book
from Jess's shelf.
"12," May Belle responded
cheekily, opening drawers.
"Why?"
Leslie shrugged her shoulders
and then closed the book.
"I just didn't
know that 6th
graders were
this..."
"Dirty?"
May Belle cut her off with a smirk.
"Well I was gonna say mature."
Earlier before they started snooping around, they
were just having that friendly girl talk with Leslie
giving girl advice to May Belle about a certain crush
of hers in school.
Strangely, the topic suddenly turned to Jess
and then stranger things, until May Belle
suggested doing something.
"Jess's 17, he's gotta have
something here!"
She bit her lower lip.
She tried looking at his drawers, in his
books, in his closets, everywhere!
But they couldn't find a single thing.
On the other hand, Leslie was feeling pretty stupid
about doing this to Jess's room.
She looked at the closet where Jess's clothes were scattered all
over the place from May Belle's rummaging.
She felt pretty bad about messing up his
room, even though she wasn't the one who
completely messed it all up.
Leslie threw a glance over to Jess's
bed, and then below it.
She might've been away from the outside world for
5 years, but she pretty much had a very open mind
when she was just 12.
"Did you try looking under his bed?"
May Belle's head perked up and instantly crawled to his
bed before literally going under it.
A few seconds later, she returned with a magazine.
A mischievous smile crept up to her lips as she raised the
magazine in her hand and showed it to her.
"Look what I
found..."
She snickered.
Jess was going to open the door to his room until he
heard giggles coming from inside.
He stopped in his tracks and decided to
stay outside for a bit.
"Oh my god, look at this!"
He heard Leslie's voice, a laugh following later.
He raised his eye brow in question as he
pressed his ear to the door.
They couldn't have, could they?
As he continued listening to that confusing things
he could hear, a voice startled him.
"What are you doing?"
Jess literally jumped up from the sound, making his
head thud against the wooden door.
"Mmm!"
He groaned in pain, not letting the
yelp escape from his mouth.
He winced as he raised his head up
to see who it was.
"Shhh!"
He held his finger to his lips, shushing his
little sister, Joyce Ann.
He kneeled down to her height and
looked straight at her.
"Don't make any sound."
He sharply whispered to her.
Joyce Ann looked at him with a puzzled expression.
Instead of nodding to his words, he walked past
him and knocked on the door.
"Hello?"
Jess immediately grabbed her by the
waist and pulled her to him.
"Didn't I say to not make a sound?"
He cried.
Footsteps came along before the door
opened, revealing Leslie.
"Oh Jess," she chirped.
Her eyes looked down at him before noticing that
he was carrying a small child.
Her eyes brightened at the sight of Joyce Ann.
May Belle could be seen in the room with her head poked
out to see what was happening.
As soon as she saw Joyce Ann, her face
turned into a frown.
He stood up from his position and went
inside with Joyce tagging along.
His eyes looked at the floor, noticing the pile of
clothes on the ground, and his books on the shelf that
was supposedly to be in order.
"What did you guys do to my room?"
May Belle rolled her eyes at him.
"Just a bit reorganizing, oh and this."
She raised the magazine up to his face and smirked.
The contents of the magazine that she and
Leslie peeked in were ...
Well, disappointing for her since she
thought that there'd be more.
Leslie laughed at the sight of Jess's face as he
grabbed the magazine in horror.
"What are you
doing with-"
She cut him off with a cheeky smile.
"You're magazine? Yeah we decided to
snoop around a little."
She looked over to Joyce Ann who had that innocent little
face ever since she got into the room.
"What's that magazine about?"
She innocently asked as she
pointed to the magazine.
She went over to Jess's bed where the rest of the girls
were at and sat next to Leslie.
May Belle looked at Joyce Ann in disgust for
some reason and rolled her eyes.
Noticing May Belle's behavior to Joyce, Leslie looked
at Jess and gave him a look before returning her
attention back to the little one.
"It's nothing."
Jess simply said.
He walked to his study table and opened one of
the drawers, shoving the magazine in it before
locking it with a key.
There
we
go...
After making sure that there weren't anymore dirty stuff of his
in the room, he let out a sigh in relief.
Leslie smiled as she leaned on the wall near the bed.
"You're so big now!"
Joyce looked at her with an innocent face.
"Have I met you before?"
She asked.
Of course she wouldn't remember, she was still a baby.
Hearing Joyce Ann's words, May Belle crossed her arms and
rolled her eyes away before letting out a sigh.
"No, of course not," she sarcastically said.
"She knows you so of course you don't know her."
"Okay May Belle, that's enough."
Jess approached them to bed and
ticked her on the forehead.
Sometimes May Belle could be harsh to Joyce, which most
of the time the older siblings would need to intervene
or else Joyce would cry.
Leslie looked back at Joyce and noticed that
she was glaring at May Belle, but also almost
at the verge of tears.
"Really May Belle?"
She said.
"What?"
May Belle asked, flabbergasted as if she was some
innocent little girl who didn't do anything.
May Belle tossed her head back and
then rolled her eyes away.
"Fine," she grunted.
"Sorry Joyce."
She reluctantly apologized
half-heartedly to Joyce.
After doing so, Joyce Ann smiled and got off
the bed, taking May Belle's hand and dragging
her out of the room.
As they watched Joyce Ann drag May Belle out the
room and into the hallway, they heard May Belle's
words of trying to stop Joyce Ann until they heard
the door shut.
"What's with all that yammering about?"
An annoyed Brenda yelled from her room, causing
both Jess and Leslie to laugh.
With May Belle and Joyce Ann now out of the
room, they were finally alone.
Jess walked to the door and closed it before
sitting on his arm chair.
"Joyce grew up fast huh?"
Leslie grinned.
She blew the strands of hair that was covering her face
and then pushed it behind her ear.
"Yeah," he replied.
"Almost too fast."
Jess raised his eye brow, "how'd you
even know that it was her?"
Leslie shifted her position
and sat crossed legged.
"Well it kinda made sense. The baby back
then and her and all..."
Jess shrugged his shoulders at her answer.
Made sense.
She met Joyce back when she was still a baby when she
came to the house to wash up after Janice squirted
ketchup all over her.
Though it's weird how she could recognize Joyce.
She looked outside his window and noticed that
the rain was now just drizzling.
"The rain has stopped."
She said.
Jess looked over to the window and
noticed it as well.
"Yeah," he quietly said.
"You wanna go home?"
"Well I'm sure that I have a lot of things to do
later for school tomorrow."
She snickered as she got up and
tidied her shirt.
She walked out of his room and down the stairs.
Jess later took another wind breaker of
his and followed her down.
When he got down, wearing his jacket, he saw
Leslie talking with his mother.
"Thanks for letting me stay here Mrs Aarons," Leslie
smiled and put her hands behind her back.
"I really appreciate it."
Mrs Aarons returned a small smile to her.
She brought her hands to Leslie's
shoulder and shook it gently.
"I'm glad you're here."
Jess quietly crept down the stairs and wore his
jacket over before getting an umbrella.
He went to the door and opened it,
looking over to Leslie.
"You ready?"
He asked.
"You don't have to walk me back ya know."
Leslie walked over to him and wore a grin.
They both walked out of the house and looked at
the muddy pools of puddles.
Jess shook his head with a chuckle as he opened the
umbrella and raised it above their heads.
He closed the door behind him.
"I insist."
"So are you actually ready?"
Jess finally asked.
They walked up to the stairs of the front porch where
there was a roof over their heads.
Leslie raised her eye brow in question as she
watched him close the umbrella.
"Ready for what?"
"Tomorrow, school of course."
He grinned.
He knocked at the front door, waiting for
one of the Burke's to answer.
Leslie folded her arms to her chest and closed her
eyes, thinking about his question.
"Yeah, I guess I am."
She nodded.
The door then opened, revealing
Judy wearing her glasses.
"Oh you're back," she looked at Leslie and noticed the
different clothes she was wearing.
"What happened?"
A laugh came out from Leslie's lips
as she looked at Jess.
"Long story mom."
She smirked.
Just remembering that her clothes was still
back at Jess's place, she blushed.
"Oh my clothes!"
Jess looked behind him and to his house.
They forgot to take Leslie's clothes
along with them when they left.
He then told her that he'd give it to her
tomorrow morning when they meet.
After exchanging words with one another,
it was time for him to leave.
He grabbed his umbrella and put it over his head
before walking out of the Burke's property and
heading out to his house.
Leslie and Judy watched him walk away as
the rain poured harder.
"Come on," Judy walked back inside the living room.
Leslie stayed behind for a few more minutes as she
stared at Jess before he changed direction and
walked back to his house.